Guide to the Herbert Feigl Papers, 1916-1973 ASP.1997.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Offprints by Others, 1903-1980; VI.
  - Wallace, William A., 1965 (Folder 51)
  - Warburg, E., 1918, 1922 (Folder 52)
  - Watanabe, Satosi, 1955, 1970 (Folder 53)
  - Watson, James D., 1968 (Folder 54)
  - Weinberg, Julius, 1950 (Folder 55)
  - Weingartner, Paul, 1964 (Folder 56)
  - Weisskopf, Victor F., 1965 (Folder 57)
  - Wellman, Carl, 1962 (Folder 58)
  - Will, Frederick L., 1947 (Folder 59)
  - Wilson, Fred, 1967, 1969 (Folder 60)
  - Wilson, N. L., 1964 (Folder 61)
  - Wisdom, J. O., 1951, 1960 (Folder 62)
  - Witte, Wilhelm, 1963 (Folder 63)
  - Yourgrau, Wolfgang, 1960 (Folder 64)
  - Zanstra, Herman, 1970 (Folder 65)
  - Zeisel, Hans, 1968 (Folder 66)
  - Zilsel, E., 1921 (Folder 67)
  - Zucker, A., 1965 (Folder 68)
  - Unidentified (Folder 69)